# **Lior Koren**

Hi, I'm Lior, 26 years old, and looking for roles as a junior full-stack software engineer. I recently finished my service in the IDF Medical Corps as a full-stack developer and biomedical engineer under the status of Returning Citizen. In my role, I developed web applications for my department and procured medical devices for the army.

I also develop my own full-stack projects.

Projects (click to view Github Repo)

- App for the IDF Championship in Medicine
- hanaref
- LanguCards

### Timeline



# Skills

Coding: React, TypeScript, Node.js, Mongo, Git, Python, MATLAB.

Tools: Redux, Chai, Figma.

Languages: English (native), Hebrew (native), colloquial Arabic (near native).

## Hobbies

Fitness, cooking, strengthening my Arabic, playing piano, video games and dancing.

# **Work Experience**

# Full-Stack Developer / Medical Procurement Engineer – IDF 2020 - 2022 Medical Corps Ramat Gan, Israel

Developed PWAs to facilitate processes previously done manually / solely through an army computer.

# Lab Technician – SBH Sciences Natick, MA, USA

2015 – 2016

Performed assays for clients developing drugs in the pre-clinical stage.

#### Education

# B.Sc. in Biomedical Engineering Tel Aviv University

2016 - 2020

I learned algorithmics and machine learning and implemented projects modeling physiological and intracellular systems using Python and MATLAB.

# Self-taught and online courses

2020 - present

I delved into full-stack web development by online courses, self-studying and building my own projects.

Among the courses I studied were:

- The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp – Dr. Angela Yu
- React The Complete Guide Max Schwarzmuller
- The Complete Developers Guide to MongoDB
   Stephen Grider
- Advanced JavaScript Asim Hussain